Abdirahman Muqtar Osman

Software Developer

QJaale Siyaad Street , Dharkeynley , Mogadishu-Somali

Cover Letter

Dears [Salaam Somali Bank],

I am writing to express my strong interest in the position Software Developer at **Salaam Somali Bank** . I have Bachelor degree in Computer Science from **Jamhuriya University**.

I have two years experience as asoftware developer a compelling and impactful way, In addition to my Software Developer proficiency, I possess skills in Database Adminstrator and graphic Designer, My graphic design skills enable me to create visually compelling content that resonates with audiences, while my Software Developement knowledge allows me to collaborate Software development teams.

Salaam Somali Bank commitment to innovation and excellence aligns perfectly with my professional values, and I am eager to contribute my skills and experience to your team. I believe that my background and expertise make me well-suited to drive impactful Development campaigns that support your Development Objectives.

Sinceraly,

Abdirahman Muqtar

Skills

Software Developer	• • • •
Web Designer	•••
Digital Marketer	• • • •
Graphic Designer	• • • •
Data management	• • •
Administrative Abilities	• • •

Languages

Somali

Native

English

Very good

Arabic

Good

Education

Bachloar Degree Computer Science,

Jamhuriya University of Scinece and technology 2019 – 2023

Diploma Digital Marketing,

Jamhuriya Incubation Center (JIC) 2023

High School Certificate,

Al-Anwaar Primary and secondary School 2015 – 2019

Diploma English language,

Al-imra Educational Institute 2013 – 2015

Diploma Health Science,

Daaf Health Training College 2015 – 2016

Certificate Computer basic program,

Al-imra Computer Institute 2016

Professional Experience

Teacher Computer Basic program,

Al-imra Educational Institute

2016 - 2017

English Teacher,

Al-imra Educational Institute

2015 - 2017

Assistant in giving prescription medications Hospitals, Daaf Hospital 2015

CEO and Founder,

Caawiye Digital Agency 2023

Refrence

Available On Request